dearfoams.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Dearfoams

Dearfoams.com Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Thank you for visiting the Dearfoams.com website. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the privacy of any personally identifiable information that we may collect from you as you use the Dearfoams.com website. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the Dearfoams.com website or our services, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. By visiting the Dearfoams.com website, you are confirming your agreement to our privacy policies as described in this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using the Dearfoams.com website or our services or transacting business with us. You should also review our Terms of Use for more information about the policies governing your use of the Dearfoams.com website. 

### Information We Collect

We may collect and store personally identifiable information on certain areas of the Dearfoams.com website when users register, purchase products or services, request information or a response, sign up for events, apply for jobs, or participate in user posting areas, such as bulletin boards, discussion forums and surveys. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, address, age, date of birth, sex, company or school affiliations, education level, e-mail address, driver's license number, telephone numbers, information about your interests and activities and your reviews of our website or products that we sell. If you transact business with us, such personally identifiable information may also include financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). You may elect not to provide certain types of information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the Dearfoams.com website. We may combine the personally identifiable information that we receive from you through the Dearfoams.com website with information from other sources. 

We may also collect and store personally identifiable about other people that you provide to us. If you use the Dearfoams.com website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient. 

We may also automatically collect and store certain types of information when you visit the Dearfoams.com website. For example, we may use "cookies" to obtain information when you access the Dearfoams.com website. Such information may include your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the date and time of your visit, the operating system of your computer and the domain name of your Internet service provider and is used to facilitate access to the Dearfoams.com website and to personalize your on-line experience. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better shopping experience. Utilities are available from third parties to help you visit websites anonymously, but use of such utilities may also result in you being unable to use certain features of the Dearfoams.com website. 

We may use standard Internet technology, such as Web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of the Dearfoams.com website. We may also include Web beacons in e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer visitors to the Dearfoams.com website to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our on-line advertising and content or other activities. 

We may allow third parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on the Dearfoams.com website. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. The Dearfoams.com website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. 

### Use of Information

Personal information that we collect from customers and users of the Dearfoams.com website is used to improve our relevance to you and to improve your shopping experience with us. We use the information that you provide so that we may provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to fulfill your requests for information, to manage our business, to process your requests to participate in events, and to review and consider any employment related inquiries that you may submit. In addition, we may send you by e-mail or offline offerings of products or services that we think may be of interest to you or ask you to participate in activities such as special surveys. We may also use personally identifiable information in analyzing the behavior of users of the Dearfoams.com website in order to measure interest in specific items posted on the website. 

We will not share any personally identifiable information that you provide to us except (i) for the purposes that you provided it to us, (ii) with us or others from injury or loss, or (iii) with other persons or entities with whom we contract to provide services in connection with the Dearfoams.com website or our other business activities. If we do share personally identifiable information with a third party, we will, to the extent practical, require that the recipient protect such information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, but we cannot guarantee how such a third party will use personally identifiable information. Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policies that describe how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about the privacy practices of those third parties, we encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States. 

We may use non-personally identifiable, summary or aggregate information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Dearfoams.com website, to enable us to further enhance your experience with the Dearfoams brand and for other business purposes. We may also share such aggregate information with third parties. 

Personally identifiable information that you have provided to us is an asset of R.G. Barry Corporation that may be included in assets transferred to an acquirer if R.G. Barry Corporation or Shoebuy is acquired by a third party or the Dearfoams is sold to a third party. 

### Third-Party Websites

We may provide links on the Dearfoams.com website to websites of third parties as a service to users of the Dearfoams.com website. In addition, some of the content appearing to be on the Dearfoams.com website may in fact be supplied by third parties. Such third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the privacy link typically located at the bottom of the Web page you are visiting. We cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection and privacy practices of such third-party websites, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. 

### Your Choices Regarding Personal Information

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the Dearfoams.com website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member, purchase products or services, participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes, ask a question, or initiate other transactions on the Dearfoams.com website. At any time, you may choose to no longer receive e-mails from Dearfoams.com by contacting us at privacy@dearfoams.com. You also will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. You may tell us not to share your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes by sending a written request to privacy@dearfoams.com or the mailing address below. 

Privacy Officer  
Dearfoams  
101 Arch Street, 16th Floor  
Boston, MA 02110 

### Access to and Correction of Personal Information

You may review, update or correct any personally identifiable information that you have provided to us through the Dearfoams.com website. You may also unsubscribe from mailing lists or any registrations on the Dearfoams.com website. To do any of such things, please either follow the instructions on the page of the Dearfoams.com website on which you have provided such information or registered, or contact us at privacy@dearfoams.com. 

### Security

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information. We want you to feel confident using the Dearfoams.com website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure e-mail. 

### Reviews and other Posted Information

We may provide areas on the Dearfoams.com website where you can post information including reviews of products. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable Web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your e-mail address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you will not be able to edit or delete such information. 

### Children's Privacy Protection

We understand the importance of protecting the privacy of children, especially in an online environment. The Dearfoams.com website is not intentionally designed for or directed at children 13 years of age or younger and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, if you are a resident of California, you have the right to control how your personal information is shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Following receipt of a request from you, we will provide you with a cost-free means of informing us that you do not want your personal information to be shared with third parties for the direct marketing purposes of such third parties. We provide you with a cost-free means of informing us that you do not want your personal information to be shared with third parties for the direct marketing purposes of such third parties. If you would like to exercise your right under California law to tell us that you do not wish your personal information to be shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, you should send your written request to privacy@dearfoams.com or the mailing address below. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

Privacy Officer  
Dearfoams  
101 Arch Street, 16th Floor  
Boston, MA 02110 

### Visiting the Dearfoams.com website from outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on the Dearfoams.com website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting the Dearfoams.com website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Consent; Modification

By using the Dearfoams.com website, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your personal information by R.G. Barry Corporation in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. Your visit to the Dearfoams.com website and any dispute concerning privacy will be subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. You agree that your visits to, and use of, the Dearfoams.com website will be subject to and bound by the then current version of this Privacy Policy. The form of our Privacy Policy in effect from time to time will apply to all information that we have collected. 

### Contact our Privacy Department

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please contact us at privacy@dearfoams.com. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: January 5, 2009.
